



Graphic Designer + Content Strategist
Marketing Specialist

PROFILE

Freelance Graphic Designer with over 8+ years of experience in managing the complete design process, from conceptualization to delivery. Creative Designer with a background in business development design. Detail-orientated in completing projects with the ability to multi-task effectively. Exceptional problem solver, communicator, driven to succeed with strong interpersonal skills, the ability to work on multiple projects at once and consistently meet production deadlines. Able to stretch the boundaries of digital storytelling to help my client's brands stand out.

CONTACT

9448 Brookmont Court Elk Grove, California 95624

P: 916.752.6881

E: tccreative@comcast.net W: www.tccreativegd.com

EXPERIENCE

JULY 2019 - PRESENT

LYON REAL ESTATE

Freelance Graphic Designer

Currently work as the point of contact for the Trigger Listing Program. Create marketing materials featuring brochures, postcards, mailings, flyer's, iconography and eBlasts for listing property. Collaborate with marketing team and Agents on the most effective way to market their listing. Create Social Media ads using Facebook, Instagram and Adfenix.

NOVEMBER 2018 - OCTOBER 2019

HOSPITALITY SOURCE, INC.

Freelance Graphic Designer

Contracted to develop numerous marketing programs (logos, mailings, infographics and advertisements). Worked closed with the management to ensure all materials exceed expectations. Managed projects/tasks while under pressure to meet weekly deadlines. Ensured quality and accuracy in all design work. Revised the work of previous designers to create a unified aesthetic for Hospitality Source's branded materials.

NOVEMBER 2017 - MARCH 2019

SAS INSTITUTE INC.

Sr. Office Administrator

Created presentations and marketing material according to company standards. Designed, developed and implemented graphic layouts and production. Worked with internal administrative applications such as Orion, Concur, or Atlas. Assisted the sales teams with process and marketing. Department liaison for several departments; continually communicated with staff regarding policies and procedures.

ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCE

WWW.ETSY.COM/SHOP/TCCREATIVE

ETSY (ONLINE STORE)

Offering custom wedding, birthday, graduation and baby shower invitations as well as custom branding and logo design.

EDUCATION

2012 - PRESENT

ASSOCIATES IN GRAPHIC COMMUNICATIONS

Sacramento City College, Sacramento, California

SKILLS

- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe InDesign
- Adobe Acrobat

- Client Consultations
- Proposals and Contracts
- WordPress
 - Macintosh and PC Literate